stardeveloper.com 2000-12-04

# Welcome to eFront

Company Overview  
Corporate Offices  
Press Room  
Strategic Partners  
Investor Relations  
Career Opportunities  
Advertising  
Contact Us  
Management  
Copyright Infringement  
Terms of Use  
Privacy Policy |  **Privacy Statement for eFront.com**   

eFront Media, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: **eFront.com** and network sites. The eFront.com, and network Web sites ("sites") are operated by eFront Media, Inc., located in Costa Mesa, California. You can reach us with questions regarding this statement via e-mail at [privacy@efront.com](mailto:privacy@eFront.com). 

Your IP address is used only when you become a member as a backup identification tool for polls and other member services. 

Our sites use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites, and for other purposes. These cookies are used soley for the sites, and the content contained is not distributed to third parties. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information related to eFront.com only when requested by said user. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. You e-mail address will never be given or sold to a third party and will only be viewed by eFront, Inc. Your pager e-mail address not be disclosed and will only be used for sending breaking news upon request. Other information you use will only be used to collect broad demographic information about our visitors. 

This site contains links to other sites. **eFront Media, Inc.** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is only used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings they have signed up for; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected on our sites. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. To find out more about how Doubleclick manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://doubleclick.com/privacy_policy>. 

This site, eFront, uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>. 

**Public Forums**

Our sites make chat rooms, forums, and message boards, available free to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff overlook server access daily to ensure the above holds true.

 **Children's Guidelines**

This site gives children between the ages of 13 and 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum. 

In order to comply with the new [COPPA ruling](http://www.cdt.org/legislation/105th/privacy/coppa.html), if you are younger than 13 years of age, you are forbidden from becoming a member of eFront or posting information on eFront message boards without direct parental consent. You may have your parent or guardian e-mail us at [permission@efront.com](mailto:permission@efront.com) to verify that you have been granted permission to use this site. 

**Choice/Opt-Out** Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [support@efront.com](mailto:support@efront.com)
  2. You can edit your preferences via the eFront.com main page

**Correct/Update** This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

Visit <http://www.efront.com/prefs.php3> to modify your surveys and user information.

**Contacting the Web Site** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, you can contact [privacy@efront.com](mailto:privacy@efront.com). For other questions regarding the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, contact [support@efront.com](mailto:support@efront.com).
